figleaves.com 2018-02-26

# Privacy Policy | Figleaves

Figleaves is a trading name of JD Williams and Company Limited. Your privacy and security is important to us. This privacy notice explains how we will use the personal information that we collect about you.

#### Your Personal Information

When you visit [www.figleaves.com](http://www.figleaves.com/) we will collect certain information about you depending on how you use the site and whether or not you are logged into your account and make a purchase. We may collect:

  * contact information, such as name, address, telephone number and email address.

This information will be used to process and fulfil your order. It will only be used for marketing purposes if you have previously consented to such use.

  * purchase information, such as credit card details.
  * information from cookies or web beacons, such as navigation and click-stream data, the time of accessing the website, duration of your visit, products you viewed or searched for, items in your basket, at which stage you abandoned your basket.

For more information about cookies and how to turn off cookies please see below.

Figleaves collates statistics about site traffic, sales and other commercial information, which we pass on to third parties to assist us in improving the services we provide to you.  We also use demographic information to tailor the website to the interests of our customers, which we share with third parties, again on an aggregate basis only so that they can build up a better picture of our customer base and general consumer trends.

We may occasionally transfer some of the information you provide outside the European Economic Area (the EEA), for example to prevent fraud. In some cases, countries outside the EEA may not have such well-developed data protection laws as those in the EEA. However, we'll put in place measures and safeguards that require your personal data to be kept secure, confidential and to be processed only and strictly in line with the terms of this privacy notice and any relevant data-protection laws.

By shopping with us and giving us your personal information, you consent to its transfer to third-party data processors including those in countries outside the EEA for relevant purposes.

From time to time we would like to contact you about other products and services that we think may be of interest to you. These products and services may be offered by Figleaves or other trading brands in the JD Williams and Company Limited group. We would also like to contact you about products and services offered by other third parties. We will ask you whether you would like to hear from us for marketing purposes and will only contact you if you agree.

You can also change your mind at any time by just letting us know. Please go to [My Account](http://www.figleaves.com/uk/account-landing.html) to update your settings. Please note that it may take a short while for the changes in your preferences to become effective.

As part of our policy to protect against the fraudulent use of credit cards, we carry out security checks on orders. These can take various forms, and may involve contacting you by telephone before your order is processed.

From time to time it may be necessary for us to ask you to provide a copy of a recent statement header for the card being used on your order. Please note that we are only interested in confirming information already provided on your order, i.e. the billing name and address and card issuer details, and do not need to see actual transactions, which can be covered up. 

If you have any concerns regarding security, please let us know. We hope you appreciate that these measures are a necessary precaution, undertaken in the interests of fraud prevention.

Our website may contain links to other third party websites. This privacy notice does not cover these links or the way that your personal data may be used by the third parties who operate these sites. Please read carefully any privacy policies on other websites you visit, particularly before providing any personal information.

This privacy notice was last reviewed and updated on 21 June 2016. We keep our privacy notice under regular review and may occasionally amend it to reflect any new regulatory requirements and changes in our information collection and use. You should therefore return here regularly to view our most up to date privacy notice.

You can request details of and a copy of the personal information that we hold about you by making a subject access request under the Data Protection Act 1998. Please contact the Data Protection Officer at the address below to make a request. A small charge may apply.

We want to make sure that all of the information we hold about you is accurate and up to date so please let us know if we have got anything wrong.

If you have any questions, concerns or comments about this privacy notice or our use of your personal information please contact us:

Data Protection Officer  
JD Williams and Company Limited  
Griffin House  
40 Lever Street  
Manchester M60 6ES

When you visit our site, a cookie may be saved on your computer (if your computer accepts cookies), and if you return to the site the cookie may be read. We use cookies to help us collect the site visitation data described above and in some cases to deliver specialised content. 

A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

Some parts of our website use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. We do not correlate this information with data about individual users, nor do we share this information or sell it to any third party.

If you prefer not to receive cookies on our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any area of our website.
